<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest news</title>
    <link>http://mysite.local/news/news.php</link>
    <item>
      <title>Harry and Meghan’s daughter Princess Lilibet christened, Charles, Camilla, William, Kate snub invite</title>
      <link>NZ Herald</link>
      <description><![CDATA[King Charles reportedly snubbed an invitation to the christening of the daughter of the Duke and Duchess of Sussex, which it’s been revealed took place in California last Friday.

It comes as the Sussexes mull whether they will go to the King’s coronation in May.

Harry and Meghan said their 21-month-old was christened “Princess Lilibet Diana” in their home town of Montecito, on the coast north of Los Angeles.

It is the first time Lilibet has been referred to as a princess.

A spokesman for the royal pair confirmed to the US’ People magazine that the ceremony took place last week.

“Princess Lilibet Diana was christened on Friday, March 3 by the Archbishop of Los Angeles, the Rev John Taylor,” a statement said.]]></description>
      <pubDate>08-03-2023 23:29:38</pubDate>
      <category>Politics</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANZ bank offers $19k settlement to pensioner who lost $36k to scammers, acknowledges victim’s stress</title>
      <link>NZ Herald</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The country’s biggest bank has made a $19,000 settlement offer to an elderly woman who was tricked into buying nearly $40,000 in pre-paid gaming cards from a Mobil service station by scammers posing as ANZ fraud prevention staff.

In a letter to the victim’s family, ANZ concedes that a fraudster posing as the woman phoned the bank’s contact centre and convinced staff to divulge personal customer information. This enabled money to be transferred between her accounts, contributing to the financial loss.

The bank also accepts it failed to record the woman’s son as having power of attorney over her financial affairs and says a delay in responding to the family’s complaint compounded her stress.

The settlement offer was “a token of our sincere regret for the way ANZ has handled aspects of your complaint and the time taken to resolve the matter”.]]></description>
      <pubDate>08-03-2023 23:13:19</pubDate>
      <category>Politics</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox News executives discussed a plan to denounce the 'Trump myth'</title>
      <link>NBC News</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By early January 2021, Fox News hosts and executives were ready to move on from then-President Donald Trump and his insistence that the election was stolen.

"it's been 8 weeks and none of them has produced anything tangible or verifiable. and now he wants thousands of his supporters to go to DC without shelter or food to demonstrate," host Lou Dobbs texted a producer on his show on Jan. 3. "I believe the election was stolen — but without evidence we can do nothing significant."

"We are very, very close to being able to ignore Trump most nights," Tucker Carlson wrote in a Jan. 4 text to an unidentified person. "I truly can't wait."

"I hate him passionately," he continued. "I can't handle much more of this."

The revealing private messages were unsealed Tuesday night, part of a massive cache of evidence in the $1.6 billion Dominion defamation suit against Fox News and the Fox Corp. They paint a remarkably frank picture of how key players at Fox News viewed the stolen election lie that motivated a mob to storm the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021.

Fox News argued the voting systems manufacturer was skewing the evidence.]]></description>
      <pubDate>08-03-2023 22:49:11</pubDate>
      <category>Politics</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter users were unable to view tweets in latest service disruption under Musk</title>
      <link>CNN</link>
      <description><![CDATA[witter’s timeline page appeared to experience a prolonged outage on Wednesday morning, marking the latest service disruption for the platform under new owner Elon Musk.

Some Twitter users who opened up their “for you” timeline were greeted with a blank screen and a message saying, “welcome to your timeline,” encouraging them to follow other users to get tweets to show up even if they already followed various accounts. Other users were met with a “Welcome to Twitter!” message as if they had just joined the platform. The “following” page also failed to load.

There were more than 4,000 user reports of issues on DownDetector, an outage tracker, as of 5:30 a.m. ET on Wednesday. Within about two hours, the issue appeared to have largely resolved. #TwitterDown was trending on the platform Wednesday morning.

The outage marked the second major glitch the platform has experienced in less than a month. Three weeks ago, Twitter users encountered various issues with the platform, including the inability to tweet, send direct messages or follow new accounts.

Twitter has experienced a range of technical glitches since Musk took over the company and laid off more than half its staff late last year. Users have previously reported issues with the app’s two-factor authentication tool, seeing replies listed above a tweet rather than below it and seeing old tweets show up repeatedly in their feed or mentions.

Some former employees raised concerns that the mass layoffs under Musk could cause the platform to break in big or small ways, after workers with knowledge of Twitter’s key systems were ousted. But Musk has continued to cut staff in an effort to boost Twitter’s bottom lime.

Wednesday’s service disruption comes after Twitter reportedly laid off another 10% of its staff earlier this week, including some engineers responsible for site reliability, according to a report from the New York Times.

It’s not clear what caused Wednesday’s apparent outage. Twitter, which eliminated much of its media relations staff last year, did not immediately respond to a request for comment about the issue.]]></description>
      <pubDate>06-03-2023 17:17:21</pubDate>
      <category>Culture</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
